{"data":[{"question":"The book is divided into five parts and each of these ________ three sections.","a":"have","b":"has","c":"will have","d":"had","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense (The book is divided into five parts).\u00a0\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Norman E. Borlaug was the first agricultural scientist to ________ The Nobel Peace Prize.","a":"receive","b":"have","c":"take","d":"accept","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Receive: to be given something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The building of the new bridge will ________ as planned.","a":"go up","b":"put up","c":"go out","d":"go ahead","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Go ahead: to start to do something, especially after planning it or asking permission to do it.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"I see the price of bread has ________ again.","a":"gone up","b":"put up","c":"gone out","d":"fallen out","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Go up = increase.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"He was caught shop - lifting but since this was his first offence he was ________ with a warning.","a":"gone out","b":"gone ahead","c":"fallen out","d":"let off","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Let somebody off (something): if someone in authority lets you off something you should do, they give you permission not to do it.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"She ________ her father; everyone says how alike they are!","a":"takes after","b":"takes off","c":"falls out","d":"lets off","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Take after: to look or behave like an older relative.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"There was a power cut and all the lights ________.","a":"went up","b":"put up","c":"went out","d":"went ahead","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Go out: to stop burning or shining.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"You look upset, Sven. Have you and Inger ________ again?","a":"gone out","b":"gone grey","c":"fallen out","d":"let off","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Fall out: to have a quarrel.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Paul, do you think you could ________ me ________ for the night? It's a bit too late to go home now.","a":"let me off","b":"go me out","c":"fall me out","d":"put me up","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Put somebody up: to stay in a place for a short time.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Children made their hair ________.","a":"go out","b":"go grey","c":"fall out","d":"d. let off","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Go : to change in some way, especially by becoming worse than before.\u00a0\n- (Hair): go grey\/white etc.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"}]}